const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Which is the largest rainforest in the world?",
        options: ["Congo Rainforest", "Amazon Rainforest", "Southeast Asian Rainforest", "Daintree Rainforest"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What process do jungle plants use to make their own food?",
        options: ["Respiration", "Transpiration", "Photosynthesis", "Fermentation"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Which layer of the rainforest gets the most sunlight?",
        options: ["Forest Floor", "Understory", "Canopy", "Emergent Layer"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "Which gas do trees in the jungle release during photosynthesis?",
        options: ["Carbon Dioxide", "Nitrogen", "Oxygen", "Hydrogen"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Which animal is known as the 'king of the jungle'?",
        options: ["Tiger", "Elephant", "Lion", "Leopard"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "Which jungle is home to the most tigers in the world?",
        options: ["Amazon Rainforest", "Sundarbans", "Congo Rainforest", "Daintree Rainforest"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What term describes animals active at night in the jungle?",
        options: ["Herbivores", "Carnivores", "Diurnal", "Nocturnal"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "Which insect is considered the most dangerous in the rainforest due to disease spread?",
        options: ["Mosquito", "Ant", "Beetle", "Butterfly"],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which rainforest layer has the least amount of sunlight?",
        options: ["Emergent Layer", "Canopy", "Understory", "Forest Floor"],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What percentage of Earthâ€™s species live in rainforests?",
        options: ["10%", "30%", "50%", "70%"],
        correct: 2
    },
];

export default questions;
